Hiii
Hey :D Long time no see!
Hey! It has been a while :D Do u have any questions?
Hey what`s up? Would u like to play a game? 🎮
Hey do u need any help? Attachment: help
I'm bored, come play with me. 😇
How is your study, no questions? 📖 ✔ ❌
I'm just reminding you, I'm here to help you. 😎 ☺
What about a quick quiz? Attachment: game
Don't you need any help? Attachment: help
You have to keep studying 👏 and I'm here to help you 🙆